+48 780 106 771 • Pawelduplagait@gmail.com • Wrocław, Dolnośląskie

Summary

As a Full-stack Developer with 2 years of commercial experience, I am well-versed in object-oriented programming and have a good understanding of frontend technologies. I have recently been focusing on improving my **Next.js** skills, particularly in **server-side rendering**.

github.com/PawelDuplaga

in linkedin.com/in/pawelduplaga

Skills

Next.js, React, Redux, Zustand, Prisma, Cypress, HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind, Typescript, JavaScript, C#, .NET, Entity Framework, Python, Git, Microservices, REST API, Unity, PostgreSQL, MongoDb

Education

Wrocław University of Science and Technology (Politechnika Wrocławska)

- Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science 06/2022
- Bachelor thesis Evolutionary Optization of Algorithms Controlling Non-Playable Characters in Games (C#, Unity)

Throughout my education, I gained proficiency in several programming languages, including Java, Python, C++, C#, Scala, Ocaml, and JavaScript. Additionally, I completed multiple coursework in <u>project management and software engineering</u>.

Experience

Rigby · **Frontend Engineer** (freelance)

06/2023 - Present

Next.js, React, Typescript, Javascript, HTML, SCSS, E-commerce, Headless CMS, Figma

I contributed to the development of e-commerce solutions for clients such as **Unitra** (Unitra.com) and **Platyna Marketplace** (Platyna.pl). My responsibilities included webapp page development and seamless integration of **Medusa.js** headless CMS with the web applications. In these projects I was focused on providing <u>rapid performance</u>, <u>prioritizing a</u> good customer experience.

Devnet · Software Engineer

05/2022 - 06/2023

.NET, Python, PostgreSQL, MongoDb, RabbitMq, Azure, React, Microservices, Design patterns

I contributed to a project aimed at creating software for **automated energy trading** within European markets, by maintaining and expanding the system by developing new **microservices**. My notable **accomplishment** involved creating a Python script for complex data manipulation, optimizing testing processes. This <u>efficiency improvement</u> resulted in <u>cost savings</u> and allowed us to <u>allocate more time to address real-time challenges</u>.

Sellintegro · C# Junior Engineer

07/2021 - 10/2021

.NET, SQL, Vbscript, Javascript, Docker

I played a key role in the development of a product that facilitated the **integration of e-commerce and ERP systems**. I joined specialized division of the company dedicated to delivering premium customer service to our largest clients. Within this team, I <u>directly engaged with clients</u> and <u>crafted tailored software solutions to meet their unique requirements</u>.

Languages: Polish (native), Eglish (C2)

Hobbies: Basketball, Technology, Modern design, Architecture